flyerca.com 2018-12-20

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy – updated April 9th, 2016**

This is the Privacy Policy for _[www.flyerca.com](http://flyerca.com/)_ (the “My Canadian Flyers”) and any service offered by us on the Flyer CA (the Services) and forms part of the terms and conditions for use of the My Canadian Flyers.

 **What Information Do We Collect?**

When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

 **Personal information you choose to provide**

For example, you may need to provide the following information:

  * Name
  * Email address

In addition to providing the foregoing information to our partners, if you choose to correspond further with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

 **Web site use information**

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.

 **How do we use the information that you provide to us?**

We use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable.

 **What Are Cookies?**

Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Web site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user’s Web browser on the user’s hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user’s transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.

 **How do we protect your information?**

Information Security. We utilize encryption/security software to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect from unauthorized access or disclosure and accidental loss, alteration or destruction.

Evaluation of Information Protection Practices. Periodically, our operations and business practices are reviewed for compliance with corporate policies and procedures governing the security, confidentiality and quality of our information.

Employee Access, Training and Expectations. Our corporate values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of customer information. In general, our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons, processes and transactions.

 **Communication opt out**

You can email us at webmaster@www.flyerca.com with questions, comments or suggestions.

 **Do we disclose information to outside parties?**

We may provide aggregate information about our customers, sales, Web site traffic patterns and related Web site information to our affiliates or reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.

 **Links to other sites**

We provide links to websites outside our [My Canadian Flyers](http://flyerca.com/), including third party vendors. These linked sites are not under our control, and we have no responsibility for the conduct of third parties outside the Website. You should review the terms and conditions of other websites, including privacy policies, before disclosing your personal information on any other website.
